asiawebdirect.com 2005-02-05

# Welcome to Asia Web Direct

### Asia Web Direct Group

Asia Web Direct Co. Ltd. and its subsidiary and associate companies operate www.latestays.com, www.phuket.com, www.bangkok.com, www.kosamui.com, www.gothailand.com, www.resort-hotels.com and many other clearly identified Web sites. We respect your privacy and value your trust in us. We will do everything in our power to earn your confidence so that you can enthusiastically use our services and recommend us to friends and family. 

### Personal Information

We do not collect the names or addresses of visitors to our Web sites. We do not sell, rent or barter mailing lists of our visitors. We do not reveal a visitor's name, address, credit card number or other personally identifying information to any phuket.com client other than the client involved in each particular transaction.

### Reservation Details

We do collect and store the names, addresses, credit card numbers and other personally identifying information of visitors who make on-line reservations. This information is collected using a secure server operating under our own Security Certificates issued by Thawte Server CA (a Verisign Company), transmitted in encrypted form and saved in a secure off-line environment. It is only used to process reservations and inform visitors of additional services, special offers, and to build features that will make the service easier and more personalized to use. 

At the customer's request, we will not send the customer any information or offers unrelated to the customer's specific transaction. 

### Cookies

We reserve the right to use "cookies" technology to reduce the time required for visitors to submit transactions. Cookies are small bits of code, usually stored on a user's computer hard drive, which enable a Web site to "personalize" itself for each user. No other company has access to our cookies. If you do not want us to use cookies when we serve you, disable them in your browser. 

For all transactions, we will employ reasonable and current Internet security methods and technologies. We encourage our participating third-party clients to adopt and honor their own consumer privacy policies. 

### **Statistics and Demographics**

We may reveal general, non-personal data about our Web site, such as number of visitors, country of origin, number of goods and services purchased, etc. 

### Amendments to Policy

Any changes to our privacy promise will be communicated through our Web site at least 7 days in advance of implementation. Information collected before changes are made will be secured according to the old privacy policy.
